dolcegabbana.com 2014-07-06

# DG

With a deed dated 19 December 2011, the companies Dolce & Gabbana Industria S.p.A., DGS S.p.A., Dolce&Gabbana Gold S.r.l. and Stotex S.r.l. were merged for incorporation in the company Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., Tax code and VAT number IT 09297890155 with registered office at Via Carlo Goldoni, Milan, Italy. Consequently, with effect from 1st January 2012, the company Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l. assumes all rights and obligations of the abovementioned companies, and continues the active and passive relations of the same. Interested parties may exercise their rights and request at any time the correction, deletion, addition or blockage of their data as per Art. 7 of Legislative Decree 196/2003 and oppose the sending of promotional, advertising or commercial material, by contacting the data controller, Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., Tax code and VAT number IT 09297890155, with registered office at Via Carlo Goldoni 10, Milan, Italy, e-mail privacy@dolcegabbana.it

Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., as the owner of dominion names including those at the address http://www.dolcegabbana.it  or in the Dolce & Gabbana Network (hereinafter the “Site”), uses the Site not only as a means to inform users about products belonging to the Dolce & Gabbana group but also as a tool for the collection of personal data.  
Therefore, in accordance with the provisions established in the Personal Data Protection Code, Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., as Data Controller (hereinafter the “Controller”), provides the following information concerning the processing of personal data both of users who only consult the Site (traffic data) and those who freely send their information via email and/or by filling in specific forms in order to access reserved sections within the Site or to receive the Controller’s newsletter.

This information is provided solely for the Site and the activities carried out by the Dolce & Gabbana company, also through its data processors, and does not extend to other websites which the user may be able to consult via links and/or activities offered by third parties.

1\. Types of data processed

1.1 Traffic data  
The computer systems and processing programs required to run the Site, during their normal operation, log certain data whose acquisition is automatic and inevitable (whenever Internet protocols are used) and which may, in combination with other information, enable users to be identified.  
Such data will be used with the sole aim of obtaining statistical information regarding the use of the Site and to verify that it is operating correctly.  
If expressly requested, such data may be used by the Public Authority to determine responsibility in the case of computer crime against the Site and/or third parties, in compliance with the relevant procedures of the appropriate Authorities.

1.2. Data provided voluntarily by individual users  
Personal information provided voluntarily by individual users via email, user interaction with the Site’s features, requests for services offered by the Site, completion of specific forms to access reserved sections of the Site.

The processing will in any event be limited, for both above categories, to common data.

2\. Processing methods and purposes

Data will be processed manually or with the aid of electronic tools for the following purposes:  
-    operations management of Site navigation and relevant access data;  
-    management of data and Site security;  
-    market research and statistical processing;  
-    staff recruitment and selection  
Furthermore, with the user’s voluntary and optional permission, the Controller may process information for the purpose of establishing individual or group profiles (user profiling) or for marketing purposes such as notification, via newsletters, emails or text messages, of the Controller’s products or of initiatives and events organised by the Controller and by other companies within the Dolce & Gabbana group, or with which said subjects are involved, including invitations to aforementioned initiatives or events. The user has the possibility of opposing this last processing purpose at any time, and request to no longer receive promotional and commercial material or information.

3\. Data storage

Personal data collected will be stored and processed via an electronic system managed by DG located in the DG head office. The other companies within the Dolce & Gabbana group, duly nominated Data Processors, may be and in fact are involved in the processing of personal data related to Site management and connected services and features.

4\. Data communication

Data will be communicated to other companies within the Dolce & Gabbana group or to professionals, independent collaborators, service companies and/or third party companies that co-operate with the Controller for the pursuit of the aforementioned purposes.  
With the user’s explicit consent, data may be transferred outside of Italian territory to other companies within the Dolce & Gabbana group that may be located in non-EU countries. In any event, whenever personal data is transferred to a country outside the EU the principles set out in the Personal Data Protection Code will be applied.

Subjects who receive the user’s personal data may process it as Data Controller, Data Processor and/or Persons in Charge of Processing according to circumstance.  
The complete list updated by the Data Processors is available from DG upon request.  
In no circumstance will data will be subject to diffusion.

5\. Automatic data collection tools

The Site uses session cookies and permanent cookies.  
Session cookies are temporary and are eliminated automatically after every visit to the Site.  
“Permanent” cookies remain on the user’s hard disk until they are eliminated. Cookies are used to enable full use of the Site and to track visits to the various pages/sections of the Site.  
Cookies are not and will not be used to obtain personal data or information relating to the user’s navigation of other sites.  
The information collected through cookies will be used purely for statistical purposes.  
The user can disable cookies at any time by selecting the appropriate setting in the web browser, though this may impede some functions of, or the possibility to interact with, the Site.

6\. Data submission

With the exception of traffic data (which is collected automatically by the system) the submission of data by the user is necessary to subscribe to the Site and to access the services and features offered by the Site and in the reserved areas. The non-submission of data will prevent the user from accessing and using said services and features.  
The submission of data for marketing purposes is always voluntary and optional. Any non-submission of data for such activities will have no consequence on the user’s possibility to use the services and features offered by the Site.

7\. Data subject’s rights

The interested party may exercise the rights recognised in Art. 7 of the Personal Data Protection Code including, but not limited to, the right to obtain a copy of processed data, their updating, modification, integration and, in certain cases, their cancellation or block. Requests for access to data pursuant to Art. 7 of the Privacy Code can be sent to Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., Via Goldini 10, 20129 Milan or via email to privacy@dolcegabbana.it. Specifically, the interested party may at any time withdraw his consent given previously during the sending of promotional and informational material, including the newsletter.

8\. Data Controller  
The data controller is Dolce & Gabbana S.r.l., legally based in Milan, Via Santa Cecilia 7. Any communication should be sent to the following email address: privacy@dolcegabbana.it.
